http://www.carroll.edu/consumer-information/privacy-policy

Skip to main content AboutConsumer Information
Privacy Policy
Consumer InformationAnnual ReportCarroll Fact BookInstitutional EffectivenessPrivacy PolicyTracDat
Consumer InformationAnnual ReportCarroll Fact BookInstitutional EffectivenessPrivacy PolicyTracDat Carroll College Website Privacy StatementYour privacy is very important to us and we are committed to protecting it.  Carroll College is the sole owner of all information collected through this website and does not sell, share, rent, or otherwise disclose this information except as described in this statement.  Use of this website is voluntary.  By visiting this website or submitting your personal information, you accept the terms described in this Policy Statement.Collection of Personal InformationWhen voluntarily submitted by our website visitors, we collect information that identifies you, such as names, postal addresses, email addresses, birth dates, gender, social security numbers, and other information provided through online forms.  We receive and store any information that you choose to enter through this website. This information is strictly voluntary—no personal information is collected unless you provide it.  If you choose not to provide personal information, you may be unable to access certain options and services that involve our interaction with you. To find out if there is an alternative way to provide information other than entering it on the website, you may contact the Helpdesk by calling (406) 447-4357 or email to helpdesk@carroll.edu. You will be directed to the appropriate office collecting the data.For website administration functions, information, other than personal information linked to a particular individual, is collected for analysis and statistical purposes. We use this automated data to obtain general statistics regarding the use of the website and its specific web pages, and to evaluate how our visitors use and navigate the website on an aggregate basis.CookiesSome of our web pages utilize “cookies.”  A “cookie” is a small text file that is sent by a website and stored on your hard drive or temporarily in your computer’s memory.  Cookies created by Carroll College web pages cannot be read by a third party.  You may disable cookies by adjusting the browser on your computer; however this website may not function properly when cookies are disabled. This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use this site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use full functionality of this website. By using this website you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purpose set out above.Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-onIf you wish to opt-out of your activity being analyzed by Google Analytics, Google has developed the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on. The add-on instructs the Google Analytics JavaScript not to send any information about the website visit to Google Analytics.If you want to opt-out, download and install the add-on for your current web browser. The Google Analytics Opt-out Add-on is available for Microsoft Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Apple Safari and Opera at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.How We Use Your InformationWe may use personal information we collect about you for the following purposes (this list may change without notice):For the purpose for which you specifically provided the personal information, for example to respond to a specific inquiry.To send you notifications about your accounts or transactions with us and to otherwise contact you with information we believe will be of interest to you.To notify you about our services.To analyze the use of this website, enhance existing features, or develop new features and services. To respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process.To facilitate interactions with third parties.Sharing Personal InformationPersonal information provided to us through this web site may be available to employees of Carroll College or to authorized third parties who provide services to Carroll College or to the users of this website (www.carroll.edu) and all sub-domains of this site.  Select third parties may be provided with personal information from this web site in order to help Carroll College fulfill its mission.  We will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third parties are obligated to protect personal information on our behalf. Your Ability to ChooseYou can let us know, upfront and at no cost, that you do not wish us to share your information with third parties for marketing purposes or to notify you about our services by sending us a written request by email to helpdesk@carroll.edu or to:Carroll CollegeAttn: CCIT Department1601 N. Benton AveHelena, MT 59625Review and CorrectionYou can review and update the personal information you have provided to us by sending an email to helpdesk@carroll.edu or writing to:Carroll CollegeAttn: CCIT Department1601 N. Benton AveHelena, MT 59625Links to Other WebsitesWe may provide links to other third-party web sites from this site.  Any such sites are regulated by the privacy policies of the providers of those web sites and not by this privacy statement.  Carroll College is not responsible for the privacy practices, security, or content of any third-party sites.SecurityWe care about protecting the security of your personal information, and we have implemented security procedures to protect the personal information that you provide to us.  However, no method of transmitting or storing electronic data is ever completely secure, and we cannot guarantee that such information will never be accessed, used, or released in a manner that is inconsistent with this policy.  You provide all such information at your own risk.How You Can Contact UsIf you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Statement, you may contact us at helpdesk@carroll.edu.Adopted by: Risk Management CommitteeDate: 10/23/2013Author: Loretta Andrews, Director of Technology
